Truth? I'm into Lolita chicks. I try to go by the elementary school whenever the little girls have PE because I love watching them so much. Such smooth, flat, innocent bodies.
I can barely contain my sandal fun when I see them. I get turned on by little elementary school girls.
Huh. That's cool.
It is? Yeah, but that's not all. I also have a serious mother complex and kiss my mom's picture before school every morning and then when I get home I change into baby clothes and baby talk.
I mean I have a pacifier and everything!
Huh.
I have a sister complex too. I make coterie sleep next to me. When she's not home I totally sneak into her room and smell her blanket. Just her blanket though. I draw the line of smelling her panties because that would be too creepy so I just stash them for later!
Well on top of that I'm not faithful. I've got like ten girls right now so I sneak out of my house all the time. How else am I gonna hit up Da Club am I right? Da Club is where you meet da ladies you feel me? And da more ladies I have da better. And when I say have them I mean do them obviously! Did that get her?
So I'll just have to exterminate all of them. You'll have to what? Are you kidding me? What the crap? Crazy. None of that got to her. I have no idea what I should do now. Look this date has just gotten started. So maybe take the whining down a notch?
I guess she's right. I don't want to accept it. But this is supposed to be us. On a date.
Pervert. That is. Like a rosebud blooming. Like a butterfly flying in the night. I can't stop the loneliness. Who knew this side of me? Who knew?
What I thought was love there? What I thought is!
Bye.
nothing
I'm so excited, Shino!
Look, it's got a cell phone!
Kotari gave it to me.
Isn't it super neat?
Super neat.
I hope it's okay that I had her put your number inside.
I wanted to call you first.
Yeah, that's fine.
Yay!
Where are you going?
I'm going four ways!
I'm going to call you!
Shino!
Hi.
Tomorrow, we should go walk around together.
Uh, do you mean like on a...
Like a date.
Right.
Sorry, but I'm going to be busy.
We are going out, aren't we?
Yeah, we sure are.
Good, that's what I thought.
I'll meet you in front of the park statue at 10 o'clock sharp.
Shino!
I forgot I don't know how to make a call!
Whoops!
Hey, what's up, big bro?
Origami asked me out on a date.
What?
Kotari?
My professional advice is just to ignore her.
I'm the one who made her think we were going out to start off with.
I don't want to hurt her feelings anymore than I probably already have.
Ugh.
Fine, whatever you want.
I guess we can just make her hate you and then you'll be off the hook.
Cool.
So, how do you like the clothes we chose for you?
Ugh, they're pretty awful.
We're at almost an hour after you were supposed to meet up with her.
I got it.
The AI setting change is complete.
I've done a lot of research to make this the worst possible date you've ever had.
All you have to do is what I say.
That's fine, I trust you.
Tell me you gave Toka something else to do, like I asked?
Yep.
I had her go buy stuff for dinner.
I need to buy some of your pork, please.
Great, but we'll keep monitoring her just in case.
We do not want you bumping into her.
You ready to make first contact?
Hmph.
Hey, there.
Oh.
Oh, good.
Huh?
I was worried something had happened to you.
Get it together.
If you let something like that bother you, you're never going to get through this.
Yeah, you're right.
Clothes.
Oh.
Uh.
Do you like mine?
Do I like yours?
Sure, I...
Because the single word counts!
Yeah, what I meant to say was that they...
suck.
Well, what would you prefer then?
Make your choices, guys!
Um, a school swimsuit with dog ears and a tail.
Here comes the beat down.
Or not.
Huh?
Where in the world did you get those clothes?
At a store nearby.
Pretty lucky, huh?
I had no idea!
What is this town coming to?
Let's go.
Huh?
Into town?
Why didn't that make her happiness meter go down?
Nice, very nice.
All of them are beyond nasty.
Your choices!
Shit-o, first option.
Uh, for a bitch like you to walk at the same level as a human is so presumptuous.
Uh, get on your hands and knees!
I said on your knees, bitch!
I didn't think those kind of couples were real.
Must be a boobie shoot or something.
Mommy, is that a dog?
Don't look. Stop pointing.
I am so sorry.
And now the pervert coming out plan just failed miserably.
That is one hard nut to crack.
Restroom.
Shido, go with three.
Won't that be sad for her?
Just do it already.
I thought you wanted this over today.
I won't let you go.
Huh?
I said that I won't let you go.
You mean you want me to do it here?
No, stop!
Pee on you?
Or would you rather I take a piss on you instead?
What?
Total pervert!
You're one to talk!
I'm going to get a drink for the vending machine.
Wait for me around here.
Sure, all right.
That is some freak job.
Makes me want to take a look inside her twisted head.
I can't take any more of this.
For once, I agree.
It's time for our last resort.
Okay, Shido, you're going to have to become her real boyfriend.
What?
If she accepts the fact that you two are dating, then you can break up with her and have an official end.
Oh, I see what you mean.
I guess I'll have to do something like that to make her hate me or she'll never let this thing go.
You've got one chance.
Practice what you want to say now while you can.
Yeah, okay.
Just one more left.
Yay!
I have to say I'm doing pretty well on my first errand.
Shido needs to give me a pat on the head for moving so fast.
All right, almost done.
Sata Andagi.
I wonder what that is.
Sounds like it's important for sure.
Oh, I should have asked Shido about this earlier.
One second thought!
That's the whole reason I have this!
Do your magic cell phone!
Now, where was that contacts list?
Let's break up.
See, to tell you the truth, I just don't love you anymore.
What? Really?
Yes.
I want this to be over.
But that's not what I want!
I hope you understand.
But I don't understand!
Do you hate me?
I do.
Yes, the fact is that I do hate you.
Oh, Shido.
What is this?
That sounds like Toka.
This is bad!
That was Toka.
There was a sudden change in her emotional state,
and her spirit powers are flowing back into her at a frightening pace.
How'd this happen?
In order for the phone we gave her to work during different emergencies,
we made it so that it would connect to the headset when she called you.
What?
No one told me that!
This is hardly the time to be complaining, Shido.
Right now you'll find her at the park just outside the shopping arcade.
Go before it's too late!
Shido, where did you run off to?
Sorry, I need you to hang there for a while.
Toka!
Hi, Shido.
I didn't mean what I said.
What?
I'm sorry.
You... you mean it?
I do.
You don't hate me, so you really don't hate me?
Of course not.
How could anybody hate you?
Then we... we don't have to be separated now at all?
No, we don't.
So we can be together forever?
Mm-hmm.
Together forever.
I'm so glad.
What do you think?
I did my errand well, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, you did awesome.
Origami?
Together.
Forever.
Um, what?
Get away from him, you!
When he said that, he was talking to me!
But that's not possible.
I'm positive that Shido was saying those things to me.
What's going on?
Oh, great.
Origami hurt everything, too?
Well, that's funny.
Origami Tobiichi's happiness meter has gone past full.
I've never seen that happen before.
Congratulations, bro.
Thank you.
Well...
Oh...
You will pay.
Horagami, go eat to your stupid head!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Take that!
I feel a little better now.
What? Just a little?
This cannot be okay.
So, I guess whining at the beginning of a date has to be your new thing or something.
You don't have time to whine, Romeo!
Here we go again.
The dates must go on.
What exactly do you think you're doing, Horagami?
I'm being with Shido. What exactly are you doing?
Stop!
Do not get in the way.
You're the one who's in the way!
Wrong. You are the one who is in the way.
Quit repeating everything I've said! You're in the way!
No, you are.
Yo.
Cool.
I know. Adorable, right?
It's Atore.
A.K.A. the Rainbow Fur Seal.
Totally wanted at the arcade.
Is that one of those gross cute things?
Hey, but listen.
I don't get what they're about.
I don't get away with saying that again.
I only speak the truth.
Lies!
They're from an animal series popular with chicks.
These are some of the different kinds.
Oh, I sorta like that one.
Nice.
That's the dream panda, Pandarone.
Sorry, hang on a sec.
Nah, don't worry about me.
Converse to your heart's content.
And I can take this time to chat with my girlfriend.
Hey, what's up, Kotori?
What do you think you're doing, jerk face?
Toka's happiness meter just dropped out of nowhere.
Don't you huh me?
Did you already forget what's gonna happen?
If Toka's emotional state becomes unstable, it's possible the spirit power you sealed off will
flow back into her.
It might be a good idea to let her blow off some steam.
Blow off some steam?
Like how?
Let's see.
She enjoyed the arcade, right?
Moragami-tobuichi!
Oh!
You big dummy!
Fun!
Which one's next?
Take that you horrible weird girl!
You're so gross!
You have an Audi!
appropriate
Black chest floozy!
Killjoy?
Oh, no.
I'm going to eat your brains and stop.
Perfect zombie!
Will you please stop that?
The arcade's a pretty fun place, Shido.
Thanks for taking me.
Make it quick, you guys.
We're gonna need to replace that with a new one ASAP.
Wait, I know them.
Ratatisker, right?
Of course, we organized with the arcade beforehand.
I don't like this.
Don't like what?
I showed Toka's happiness meter rising smoothly,
but her uneasiness numbers remain high.
It appears she's rather worried about something.
Fine, well, why don't we let her play some more and see what happens?
Hey, what's that game, Shido?
This should be fun.
Go take a cute picture together.
It's called a photo booth.
Basically, it takes pictures of you.
It takes pictures?
What's wrong?
It's just...
I'm not really comfortable taking those picture things.
Wait, seriously?
Well, let's do something else.
It's fine.
Shido, I'll do it if you want a picture of me.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Just this once.
I'll do it for you, Shido.
Hold on, what about me?
Don't come in here!
Hold your horses, you stupid, stupid boy!
I'm confused.
I had no clue she was camera shy.
I only took her picture that once during my examination of her.
So yeah, that must be it.
Hi, you all done?
Or...
Please don't look at it here.
Oh.
Okay.
Oh my god.
Did you guys hear there's like a couple going around breaking all the machines?
I heard the girl's the one breaking stuff.
That's so lame.
I'm out of coins.
I'll be back.
Make sure you're by yourself when you look at that picture, okay?
Sure, okay.
Oh, this?
If you want one, I can get it for you.
No!
What's the point if I don't do it myself?
Go for it.
You've done the green game before anyway.
I bet you can get it.
Yes!
Oh look, I did it, Shido!
Nicely done, Toka.
Crap.
I think it might have gotten stuck.
I'll get someone who works here.
Are you ready to go home, Shido?
Yes.
Good.
The exchange is complete.
Let's play.
I want to give this to you.
You do?
I do.
I'm not exactly sure how to explain why.
I guess it's because...
I want you to have it so you won't hate me anymore.
What?
I don't hate you.
But at school, Urikami told me that you hated me.
It is impossible for humans to ever accept spirits who kill the world.
And Shido, well, he definitely hates spirits.
That's what this is about.
So then that's the truth?
Absolutely not.
Absolutely?
Absolutely.
Really?
Absolutely?
Yep.
Really absolutely.
Really absolutely?
Like, for real?
Really absolutely, really absolutely.
Like, for real, for real.
Plus, I wouldn't go on a date with someone that I...
that I didn't like.
Huh?
That's true.
I feel the same way.
You hang on to that, Touka.
Huh?
Like a memento for today.
Yes.
Yes, I will.
75 points.
I guess that counts as passing.
What's with you, Touka?
You're in a good mood today.
Yeah!
I can't help it.
Shido took me out to a fun place yesterday.
Well, all right.
Way to go, Shido.
There was punching and hitting in random bones,
and it felt so good.
He did what?
Where the hell did that creep take you?
No, wait!
It's not how it sounds!
Oh, for Touka!
That is so lame!
You can have this back.
Oh, thank you.
I left this in my pocket and forgot all about it.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
Why'd you break my picture here?
Why are you naked?
Because Reyna told me I was supposed to take my clothes off when I took a picture.
You guys, it was just a misunderstanding!
Good morning.
So, here.
Huh?
It's for you.
Oh, you really didn't have to.
Just take it.
Okay.
Thank you.
Now we match.
Wait up, Shido!
You can't just leave this picture behind!
Huh!
Like we match!
We match!
In the universe!
deren
Bella
sicher
The
Thank you.